http://www.theborgata.com/underage-policy

Sign Up
Sign up for a new account.I am a new member.
Activate my online account.I am an existing member.
Hotel
Rooms & Suites
Classic Room at BorgataGrande Room at BorgataFiore Suite at BorgataOpus Suite at BorgataPiatto Suite at BorgataClub Room at The Water ClubVista Room at The Water Club
Amenities
Packages
Pools
The Water Club Hotel
Gift Cards
Dining
Fine Dining
Angeline by Michael SymonBobby Flay SteakIzakaya by Michael SchulsonOld Homestead Steak House
Casual Dining
Our Chefs
Events
BorgataEats
Room Service
Shows
Events
All EventsConcertsComedyNightlifeDiningComedy ClubOUT at Borgata
The Box Office
Venues
Event CenterThe Music Box
Book
Only rooms will be returned that can accommodate your party size. You will be unable to book a room with an occupancy limit lesser than your party size.
Rooms
Dining
Tickets
get more deals with
Find specials on room offers and get rewards for the money you spend
Log InSign Up
No, Thanks. Continue
SelectCheck-In
SelectCheck-Out
Guests
Mobility Accessible
Hearing Accessible
Find A Room
get more deals with
Find specials on room offers and get rewards for the money you spend
Log InSign Up
No, Thanks. Continue
SelectDate
SelectTime
4:00 PM
4:15 PM
4:30 PM
4:45 PM
get more deals with
Find specials on room offers and get rewards for the money you spend
Log InSign Up
No, Thanks. Continue
Search ByEvent
View ByDate
This week
This weekend
Pick a date
View Event Calendar
share
facebook
twitter
google+
pinterest
Atlantic City Gambling, Casino & Hotel Age Requirements
What is the Legal Gambling Age in Atlantic City, NJ?
A person must be 21 years of age to gamble at a casino in New Jersey.
What is the Age Requirement for the Hotel?
You must be 21 years of age or older to reserve a room at Borgata. Persons under the age of 18 must be accompanied by an adult at all times.
Are Kids/Babies Allowed at Borgata Hotel Casino & Spa?
The following exceptions apply to minors who are at least 8 years of age and accompanied by an adult at least 18 years of age:
Restaurant reservations for:
Old Homestead Steakhouse
Izakaya
Angeline
Bobby Flay Steak
Wolfgang Puck American Grille
and
Attending a convention function
Attending a performance in The Event Center or Music Box
Strollers are allowed for hotel guests only, however strollers are not permitted at any time in the restaurants listed above.
Age Policy
Pursuant to law, persons under the age of twenty-one (21) are not permitted to gamble at our property or loiter in casino areas. Similarly, our website is not intended for persons under the age of twenty-one (21). In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Act, persons younger than 21 years of age are not allowed to use our site, accept offers, or win contests, and we do not knowingly collect information from such persons. We reserve the right to verify age at any time for any reason and may reject a person who does not have valid age identification at any time while conducting business at the Borgata.
Changes to Policy
We reserve the right to modify or change this policy at any time, by posting such changes on the site. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting.
Email Updates
Sign up for emails
Location Information
driving directions
General Information
call us  609.317.1000
I want to
Buy a Gift CardBook a RoomBook a TableBuy Tickets
FAQs
Hotel ReservationsDining ReservationsFly Borgata Charter ProgramView All FAQs
Retail
BoutiquesGift ShopSpecialtyJewelry & Watches
Spas
Spa ToccareImmersion SpaSpa PackagesThe SalonThe Barbershop
Nightlife
Gypsy BarAll BarsPremier NightclubBETMGM Sportsbook & BarLevel One
Meetings
Our ServicesMeeting & Event SpaceMeet at The Water ClubSpecial OccasionsGroup DiningPlan Your Event
Borgata Sites
OUT at BorgataBorgata JobsFly BorgataBorgata BlogBorgataFreeCasino.comCharitable Contributions
About UsContact UsPress ReleasesResponsible GamingUnderage PolicyInvestor RelationsSitemapTerms of UsePrivacy Policy - Interest-based AdvertisingDo Not Sell My Personal Information (CA residents only)
© 2020 Borgata Hotel Casino & Spa. All Rights Reserved. | Bet with your head. Not over it. Gambling Problem? Call 1.800.GAMBLER.
BELLAGIO®
ARIA®
VDARA®
MGM GRAND®
THE SIGNATURE AT MGM GRAND®
MANDALAY BAY®
DELANO™ LAS VEGAS
PARK MGM
Cookie Policy
This site uses functional cookies. In some jurisdictions (like the US), other cookies (e.g., analytic or advertising cookies) may also be used (or authorized for third party use). By using this site, you agree to these terms. We updated our Privacy Policy.
Sections 3 & 5 of our Privacy Policy describe the categories of personal information we collect & how they may be used.
We use cookies which vary by type & jurisdiction.
Sections 1.B. and 2 of our Privacy Policy describe cookies we use & how to manage them. Read our privacy policy learn more.
